Guide to the UE National Office Records Relating to District 3 and District 3 Locals, 1936-1990s UE.4.1.3
ULS Archives & Special Collections
UE National Office Records Relating to District 3 and District 3 Locals
1936-1990s
ULS Archives & Special Collections
United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America
UE.4.1.3
12 Linear Feet (approx. 10 boxes)
This series contains files on United Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers of America (UE) District 3 and its locals collected by the UE national office. Included are correspondence, publications, minutes, and news clippings regarding local strikes, events, and organizing efforts.
Previous Citation
UE National Office Records Relating to District 3 and District 3 Locals, 1936-1990s, UE.4.1.3, Archives Service Center, University of Pittsburgh
Scope and Content Notes
District 3 of the United Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers of America (UE) consisted of locals in the majority of New York state, excluding New York City, and are now part of the UE's Eastern Region. This series contains files on UE District 3 and its locals collected by the UE national office. Included are correspondence, publications, minutes, and news clippings regarding local strikes, events, and organizing efforts. Most of the correspondence is between UE national officers and district or local officers. This finding aid will be updated with a container listing as the project progresses.
Arrangement
This series has been arranged into two subseries. The first contains records pertaining to District 3. The other subseries contains records pertaining to specific locals within the district, and are further arranged numerically by local number into sections.
Access Restrictions
No restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Gift of the United Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers of America in 1975, 1986, 1997, and 2001.
Related Material
UE District 3 Records, 1940s-1950s, UE.15.3, Archives & Special Collections, University of Pittsburgh Library System
Labor unions -- New York (State) -- History -- 20th century; Labor; Electric industry workers -- Labor unions -- New York (State) -- History -- 20th century; Labor unions -- United States -- History -- 20th century; Electric industry workers -- Labor unions -- United States -- History; Emspak, Julius; United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America. District 3; United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America; Matles, James J.
- District 3, 1.
  - District 3 Constitutions, 1937-1948 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - District 3 Constitutions, June 15, 1943-March 9, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - District 3 Constitutions, December 19, 1944-October 17, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - District 3 Constitutions, October 29, 1942-November 6, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - District 3 Constitutions, January 21, 1944-February 9, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - District 3 Constitutions, January 14, 1943-March 9, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - District 3 Constitutions, May 1, 1945-December 12, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - District 3 Executive Board Minutes, April 5, 1942-November 25, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Minutes, April 5, 1942-October 24, 1947; 1-3.
    - Minutes with January 7, 1948 Charles Rivers Letter and January 13, 1948, Letter to District Council 3, January 14, 1948; 4.
    - Minutes, October 16, 1948-November 25, 1950; 5-8.
  - District 3 Executive Board Minutes, January 20, 1951-June 16, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Minutes, January 20, 1951-April 17, 1953; 1-9.
    - Minutes with Statement of District 3 Executive Board, June 16, 1953; 10.
  - District 3 Executive Board Minutes, July 23, 1953-July 29, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Minutes, July 23-October 29, 1953; 1-2.
    - Minutes with Press Release and District 3 Cordiner Order Statement, January 14, 1954; 3.
    - Minutes, April 9, 1954-January 14, 1955; 4-6.
    - Minutes with District 3 Labor Unity Statement, April 15, 1955; 7.
    - Minutes, July 29, 1955; 8.
  - District 3 Executive Board Minutes, October 21, 1955-January 20, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - District 3 Executive Board Resolutions, October 25, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Resolution Regarding Labor Unity, October 25, 1947; 1.
  - District 3 President Leo Jandreau, January 26, 1940-April 13, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Leo Jandreau to All District Delegates Regarding District Council Meeting, January 26-February 14, 1940; 1-2.
    - Jandreau to All District 3 Locals Regarding Rome Organization and General Electric Collective Bargaining with Vote Card, March 28, 1940; 3.
    - Jandreau to All District 3 Locals Regarding Political Action and National Labor Relations Act with April 4, 1940, Julius Emspak to UE General Vice-President, April 5, 1940; 4.
    - Jandreau to All District 3 Delegates Regarding District Council Meeting, September 15, 1941; 5.
    - Jandreau to All District Locals Regarding Ladies Auxiliaries, August 31, 1941; 6.
    - Jandreau to UE Convention, September 21, 1944; 7.
    - Jandreau to All Locals Regarding Remington-rand Strikes, January 9, 1948; 8.
    - Jandreau to All Locals and Staff Regarding District Defense Fund, January 22, 1948; 9.
    - Jandreau to All Locals Regarding Political Action and 1948 Lecturs with January 15, 1948, District 3 Statement, January 22, 1948; 10.
    - Jandreau to Locals Regarding United Auto Workers Inter-union Rivalry with Charles Rivers Letter to Locals, April 10, 1948, District 3 Resolutions Against UAW Official's Raiding, and April 10, 1948, District 3 Resolution Supporting Miners' Strike for Adequate Pension, April 13, 1948; 11.
  - District 3 President Leo Jandreau, November 1, 1948-February 16, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Leo Jandreau to All Locals Regarding Remington-Rand Strikes and United Auto Workers Inter-union Rivalry with Jandreau Letter to Brothers and Sisters, July 26, 1947, Remington-Rand Contracts, and Congressional Record Excerpt, November 1, 1948; 1.
    - Jandreau to James Matles Regarding Factionalism and Local 301, March 9, 1941; 2.
    - Jandreau to All Locals Regarding District 3 Constitutions, November 8, 1949; 3.
    - Jandreau to All Locals Regarding Political Action with February 15, 1950, Districts 3 and 4 Hearing on Proposed State Budget Submitted Statement, February 16, 1950; 4.
  - District 3 President Lewis King, 1950-1951 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Lewis King to All Locals Regarding District 3 Meeting, December 1950; 1.
    - King to All Locals Regarding Wage Freeze and Political Action, January 10, 1951; 2.
    - King to All Locals Regarding District 3 Meeting, January 1951; 3.
    - King to All Locals Regarding Local 304 Tonawandas Remington-Rand Strikes, January 1951; 4.
    - King to All Locals Regarding National Conference and IUE Inter-inion Rivalry, January 30, 1951; 5.
    - King to All Locals Regarding National Conference, January 1951; 6.
    - King to All Locals Regarding Defense Cases and Trials, February 8, 1951; 7.
    - King to All Locals Regarding District Council Meetings, March 27-April 16, 1951; 8-9.
    - King to All Locals Regarding Fair Employee Practices Commission with FEPC Questionnaire, April 30, 1951; 10.
    - King to All Locals Regarding American Safety Razor Strikes with "We Can't Eat Razors" Leaflet, May 19, 1951; 11.
    - King to Stanley Scansciainte Regarding Political Action, June 5, 1951; 12.
    - King to All Locals Regarding District Council Meetings, June 15, 1951; 13.
    - King to All Locals Regarding Smith Act, June 19, 1951; 14.
    - King to Brothers and Sisters Regarding IUE Inter-union Rivalry with "This is Treason!" Leaflet, June 23, 1951; 15.
    - King to All Locals Regarding District Council Meeting, June 25, 1951; 16.
  - District 3 President Lewis King, July 5-December 17, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Lewis King to All Locals Regarding District Council Meeting, July 5, 1951; 1.
    - King to Staff Regarding Staff Meetings, July 11, 1951; 2.
    - King to All Locals Regarding Dahlstrom Metallic Door Strikes with "Help us Win" Leaflet, July 11, 1951; 3.
    - King to All Locals Regarding Buffalo Strikes, September 6, 1951; 4.
    - King to All Locals Regarding IUE Inter-union Rivalry and Schenectady National Labor Relations Board Elections, September 10, 1951; 5.
    - King to Staff Regarding Staff Meeting, September 28, 1951; 6.
    - King to All Locals Regarding District Council Meeting, September 28, 1951; 7.
    - King to All District 3 Locals Regarding District Council Meeting, October 5, 1951; 8.
    - King to District 3 Staff Regarding Local 1581 IUE Cheektowaga Westinghouse Strikes with King Telegram to James Carey and October 16, 1951, Carey Telegram to King, October 17, 1951; 9.
    - King to All District 3 Locals Regarding District Council Meeting, October 19, 1951; 10.
    - King to All Local Unions Regarding UE Fighting Fund with UE Fighting Fund Campaign Material, November 9, 1951; 11.
    - King to All Local Unions Regarding Local 326 Markel Electric Strikes, November 23, 1951; 12.
    - King to District 3 Locals Regarding District Council Meetings, December 17, 1951; 13.
  - District 3 President Lewis King, December 20, 1951-September 30, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Lewis King to District 3 Locals Regarding District Council Meeting, December 20, 1951-January 5, 1952; 1-2.
    - King to District 3 Locals Regarding Political Action, January 14, 1952; 3-4.
    - King to District 3 Locals Regarding Local 362 Markel Electric Strikes, January 16, 1952; 5.
    - King to District 3 Fighting Fund Committee Regarding UE Fighting Fund, February 13, 1952; 6.
    - King to District 3 Locals Regarding UE Fighting Fund, February 13, 1952; 7.
    - King to District 3 Locals Regarding Anti-communism and Humphery Committee, February 15, 1952; 8.
    - King to District 3 Locals Regarding District Council Meeting, March 21-April 3, 1952; 9-10.
    - King to District 3 Locals Regarding District Council Meeting with Reservation Card, April 15, 1952; 11.
    - King to District 3 Locals Regarding District Council Meeting, April 25, 1952; 12.
    - King to District 3 Council Delegates Regarding District Council Meeting, June 19, 1952; 13.
    - King to District 3 Locals Regarding District Council Meeting with Questionnaire, June 30, 1952; 14.
    - King to District 3 Locals Regarding Wages Stabilization Board, July 7, 1952; 15.
    - King to District 3 Council Delegates Regarding District 3 Council Delegates, July 9, 1952; 16.
    - King to All Locals Regarding 1952 UE Convention, July 30, 1952; 17.
    - King to District 3 Staff Regarding Publications, August 5, 1952; 18.
    - King to District 3 Locals Regarding International Harvester Strikes, August 28, 1952; 19.
    - King to District 3 Locals Regarding District Council Meetings, September 30, 1952; 20.
  - District 3 President Lewis King, October 7, 1952-October 29, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Lewis King to District 3 Locals Regarding District Council Meeting with Registration Card, October 7, 1952; 1.
    - King to District 3 Locals Regarding District Council Meeting, October 8, 1952; 2.
    - King to District 3 Locals Regarding International Harvester Strikes, Local 311 General Cable and Local 113 Marathon Electric, October 22, 1952; 3.
    - King to Local Presidents Regarding National Negro Labor Council, October 29, 1956; 4.
    - King to Local Union Officers Regarding International Harvester Strikes, November 1952; 5.
    - King to District 3 Locals Regarding New York Legislative Conference and Political Action, November 20, 1952; 6.
    - King to District 3 Locals Regarding New York Legislative Conference and Political Action with Proposed UE 1953 Legislative Conference, November 28, 1952; 7.
    - King to District 3 Locals Regarding District Council Meeting, December 22, 1952; 8.
    - King to District 3 Staff Regarding Staff Meeting, February 13, 1953; 9.
    - King to District 3 Local Presidents Regarding International Association of Machinists, IUE and Labor Unity with December 28, 1955, E.R. White Letter to All Grand Lodge Representatives and Michael Jimanez Letter to District 3 Field Organizers, January 6, 1956; 10.
  - District 3 Secretary Frank Bloom, January 1938-November 1940 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Announcement Regarding District Council Meeting, January 1938-November 1940; 1-11.
  - District 3 Secretary/Treasurer Jack Walter, October 27, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Jack Walter top All Members of District Executive Board, October 27, 1943; 1.
  - District 3 Secretary/Treasurer Jerold Mooney, November 13, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Jerold Mooney to All Western New York UE Locals Regarding Western New York Conference, November 13, 1947; 1.
  - District 3 Executive Secretary Charles Rivers, January 1945-July 1949 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Charles Rivers to All Members and Friends Regarding Remington Rand Strikes, June 28, 1947; 1.
    - Rivers to All UE Remington Rand Locals Regarding Remington Rand Conference Board, January 16, 1945-August 20, 1947; 2-3.
    - Rivers to All Locals Regarding New York Legislative Conference, January 22, 1948; 4.
    - Rivers Letter to All Locals Regarding Remington Rand and Political Action, January 26, 1948; 5.
    - Rivers to Locals Regarding Taft-Hartley and Remington Rand with Status of Labor Organization Official Government Rules, January 28, 1948; 6.
    - Rivers to All Locals Regarding Singer Strikes and Political Action with July 27, 1949, Letter to All Locals, Sample Petition, Sample Leaflet, Sample Public Leaflet and District 3 Unemployment Bulletin, July 1949; 7.
  - District 3 District Representative Emanuel Fried, March 16, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Emergency Officers and Stewards Report Regarding Local 312 Durez Collective Bargaining, March 16, 1948; 1.
  - District 3 Legislative Representative Milo Lathrop, January 1948 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Milo Lathrop Letter to District 3 Locals Regarding Political Action with City State Finances and 1948, State Legislate Bulletin, January 1948; 1.
  - District 3 District Council Minutes, November 20, 1937-March 18, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Minutes with November 22, 1937, Frank Bloom Letter to James Carey, November 20, 1937; 1.
    - Minutes, January 15-March 19, 1938; 2-4.
    - Minutes with April 25, 1938, Bloom Letter to All Secretaries and Delegates, April 23, 1938; 5.
    - Minutes, March 18, 1939; 6.
  - District 3 District Council Minutes, September 24, 1938-March 18, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Minutes, September 24-November 26, 1938; 1-3.
    - Minutes with March 13, 1939, Frank Bloom Letter to Brother, January 21, 1939; 4.
    - Minutes, March 18, 1939; 5.
  - District 3 District Council Minutes, June 10-December 2, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Minutes, June 10-August 19, 1939; 1-2.
    - Minutes with District 3 Council Delegates and Financial Statement, October 7, 1939; 3.
    - Minutes with Mailing List, December 2, 1939; 4.
  - District 3 District Council Minutes, January 20-April 20, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Minutes, January 20, 1940; 1.
    - Minutes with Mailing LIst, March 2, 1940; 2.
    - Minutes, April 20, 1940; 3.
  - District 3 District Council Minutes, June 22, 1940-February 1, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - District 3 District Council Minutes, April 19-August 2, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Minutes, April 19, 1941; 1.
    - Minutes with Financial Statement and Mailing List, June 14, 1941; 2.
    - Minutes with Financial Statement and Mailing List, August 2, 1941; 3.
  - District 3 District Council Minutes, October 4, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Minutes with Financial Statement and Mailing List, October 4, 1941; 1.
  - District 3 District Council Minutes, June 12, 1943-January 15, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Minutes with Digest of Legislative Report, June 12, 1943; 1.
    - Minutes with Stanton, Fiorillo and DeGirolamo Executive Board Appeal Report and Recommencation, January 15, 1949; 2.
  - District 3 District Council Minutes, January 15, 1949-July 21, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Minutes, January 15, 1949; 1.
    - Minutes with Minutes Correction, General Officers Endorsement and Taft-Hartley Law, July 23, 1949; 2.
    - Minutes, January 20-July 21, 1951; 3-5.
  - District 3 District Council Minutes, October 27, 1951-April 18, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - District 3 District Council Minutes, July 24-October 30, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - District 3 District Council Minutes, January 15-April 10, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - Minutes with Cordiner Order Statement, Janauary 15, 1954; 1.
    - Minutes, April 10, 1954; 2.
  - District 3 District Council Minutes, July 24, 1954-April 16, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - District 3 District Council Minutes, July 30-October 22, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - District 3 District Council Resolutions, June 12, 1943-October 25, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - Resolution Regarding Congress of Industrial Organizations, June 12, 1943; 1.
    - Resolution Regarding John C. Lewis, June 12, 1943; 2.
    - Resolution Regarding Political Action, June 12, 1943; 3.
    - Resolution Regarding Smith-Connally Bill, June 12, 1943; 4.
    - Resolution Regarding Subsidies, June 12, 1943; 5.
    - Resolution Regarding Taxation, June 12, 1943; 6.
    - Resolution Regarding War, June 12, 1943; 7.
    - Resolution Regarding Factional Disruption, October 25, 1947; 8.
    - Resolution Regarding Foreign Policy, October 25, 1947; 9.
    - Resolution Regarding UE Contract Minimum Requirements, October 25, 1947; 10.
    - Resolution Regarding Organizing the Organized, October 25, 1947; 11.
    - Resolution Regarding Political Action Committee, October 25, 1947; 12.
    - Resolution Regarding Taft-Hartley, October 25, 1947; 13.
    - Resolution Regarding Veterans, October 25, 1947; 14.
    - Resolution Regarding Wages, October 25, 1947; 15.
  - District 3 District Council Resolutions, 1948-1949 (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - Resolution Regarding International Officers Commendation, 1948; 1.
    - Resolution Regarding Political Action, 1948; 2.
    - Resolution Regarding Raiding, 1948; 3.
    - Resolution Regarding Social Security, 1948; 4.
    - Resolution Regarding General Officers Endorsement, July 23, 1949; 5.
    - Resolution Regarding Taft-Hartley Law, July 23, 1949; 6.
    - Resolution Regarding Labor Unity, July 23, 1949; 7.
    - Resolution Regarding Political Action, July 23, 1949; 8.
    - Resolution Regarding Foreign Policy, July 23, 1949; 9.
    - Resolution Regarding Social and Labor Legislation, July 23, 1949; 10.
    - Resolution Regarding Civil Rights, July 23, 1949; 11.
    - Resolution Regarding General Executive Board Endorsement, July 23, 1949; 12.
    - Resolution Regarding Unemployment, July 23, 1949; 13.
  - District 3 District Council Resolutions, July 24, 1953-April 10, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 41)
    - Resolution Regarding Peace and Jobs, July 24, 1953; 1.
    - Resolution Regarding Reaffirm Principles of International Union, July 24, 1953; 2.
    - Resolution Regarding Farmer-Labor Unity, July 24, 1953; 3.
    - Resolution Regarding Fair Employee Practices Commission, July 24, 1953; 4.
    - Resolution Regarding Freedom, July 24, 1953; 5.
    - Resolution Regarding Labor Unity, July 24, 1953; 6.
    - Resolution Regarding Political Action and Legislation, July 24, 1953; 7.
    - Resolution Regarding Speedup, July 24, 1953; 8.
    - Resolution Regarding UE Economic Policy, July 24, 1953; 9.
    - Resolution Regarding UE International Constitution Proposed Amendment with August 11, 1953, Lewis King Letter to District 3 Locals, July 24, 1953; 10.
    - Resolution Regarding Mastriani-Stewart Explosions, April 10, 1954; 11.
  - District 3 District Council Resolutions, July 24, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - Resolution Regarding the Fight for Jobs, July 24, 1954; 1.
    - Resolution Regarding Foreign Policy, July 24, 1954; 2.
    - Resolution Regarding Fair Employee Practices Commission, July 24, 1954; 3.
    - Resolution Regarding Labor Unity, July 24, 1954; 4.
    - Resolution Regarding McCarthism, July 24, 1954; 5.
  - District 3 District Council Resolutions, July 24, 1954-August 16, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 43)
    - Resolution Regarding Organize the Unorganized, July 24, 1954; 1.
    - Resolution Regarding Political Action, July 24, 1954; 2.
    - Resolution Regarding Womens Rights, July 24, 1954; 3.
    - Resolution Regarding Civil Liberties, August 16, 1955; 4.
    - Resolution Regarding Economic Police, August 16, 1955; 5.
    - Resolution Regarding Fair Employment Practices, August 16, 1955; 6.
    - Resolution Regarding Fight Against Speedup, August 16, 1955; 7.
    - Resolution Regarding Labor Unity, August 16, 1955; 8.
  - District 3 District Council Resolution, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 44)
    - Resolution Regarding Political Action, August 16, 1955; 1.
    - Resolution Regarding Peace and Foreign Policy, 1955; 2.
    - Resolution Regarding Basic UE Police Reaffirmation, 1955; 3.
    - Resolution Regarding Short Work Week, 1955; 4.
    - Resolution Regarding Taxes, 1955; 5.
  - District 3 Staff Member Directory and Assignments, October 1, 1941-October 1, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - District 3 Convention, March 21, 1942-December 31, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - District 3 Convention, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - District 3 Convention, January 5, 1948-October 8, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - District 3 Incoming Willard Bliss Correspondence, October 13, 1942-July 15, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 49)
    - Julius Emspak Regarding Finances, October 13, 1942-February 23, 1943; 1-2.
    - Emspak Regarding 1943 UE Convention, June 10, 1943; 3.
    - Emspak Regarding Charters with Existing Charters, July 7, 1943; 4.
    - Leo Jandreau to Willard Bliss Regarding Political Action and American Labor Party with July 14, 1943, Ruth Young to Jandreau, July 15, 1943; 5.
  - District 3 Outgoing Willard Bliss Correspondence, November 12, 1942-September 22, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 50)
    - Willard Bliss to James Matles Regarding Publicity, November 12, 1942; 1.
    - Bliss to Julius Emspak Regarding 1943 UE Convention, June 9, 1943; 2.
    - Bliss to Emspak Regarding Charters, July 6, 1943; 3.
    - Bliss to Leo Jandreau Regarding District Council and District 3 Constitutions with Constitutional Recommendations and Proposed District Council Meetings Agenda, July 8, 1943; 4.
    - Bliss to Emspak Regarding Per Capita, Unemployment, Wages, War Labor Board and Locals 309, 311, 321 and 323, August 3, 1943; 5.
    - Bliss to Jandreau Regarding Finances, August 31, 1943; 6.
    - Bliss to Emspak Regarding Finances, October 21, 1943; 7.
    - Bliss Telegram to Harriet Warren Regarding Delco, November 11, 1943; 8.
    - Bliss to Emspak Regarding Staff Finances, December 20, 1943; 9.
    - Bliss to Emspak Regarding Staff Finances, December 21, 1943; 10.
    - Bliss to Emspak Regarding Conscription and Staff Members, December 21, 1943; 11.
    - Bliss to David Scribner Regarding Ingersoll Rand Organization and International Association of Machinists Inter-union Rivalry, December 21, 1943; 12.
    - Bliss to Jandreau Regarding Local 325 Amalgamations, Tonawandas Labor Council and Factionalism, January 3, 1944; 13.
    - Bliss to Jandreau Regarding Local 325 Amalgamation and Factionalism, January 3, 1944; 14.
    - Bliss to Lou Sarti Regarding Standard Gage, National Labor Relations Board and Unfair Labor Practices, January 6, 1944; 15.
    - Bliss to Jandreau Regarding Standard Gage and National Labor Relations Board, January 17, 1944; 16.
    - Bliss to Jandreau Regarding Staff Meeting with Bliss Letter to All Organizers, January 17, 1944; 17.
    - Bliss to Jandreau Regarding Johnson City Rem-Rand and Stewards Banquet, February 5, 1944; 18.
    - Bliss to Jandreau Regarding Military Personnel, February 14, 1944; 19.
    - Bliss to Emspak Regarding Staff Members, September 22, 1944; 20.
  - District 3 Incoming Leo Jandreau Correspondence, October 26, 1939-November 15, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 51)